### Contact

7/13EMKstreet nanganallur Chennai 7550136698 (Mobile) rajeshkumarkesavan586@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/ rajeshkumar586 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Python
Digital Marketing
Java

## Languages

Tamil (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Limited Working)
English (Full Professional)

building robots with tjbot

#### Certifications

mathematics for machine learning from imperial college london online digital marketing
Cisco Certified Network Associate
Routing and Switching (CCNA)
machine learning specialisation from

university of washington(4courses)

### Honors-Awards

Quiz competition at college level first prize

python programming competition at college level

# Rajeshkumar k

Data Scientist/ Machine Learning Aspirant/ AI tech talks/Developed Project in 5 hack-a-thon /Learning about business and open to opportunities/ Writer/ Analyst.

Chennai

# Summary

I found myself creative with a open attitude towards learning new things. I personally feel experiences about life determines our perspectives. I have huge interest to break a certain problems into chunks of data and gaining insights from it. My mind gets running on and on, in solving a problem . whenever i was given a problem, i come up with various strategies and ideas to tackle it to provide mindful solution.

# Experience

Techstars Startup Weekend Memebr February 2020 - Present (7 months) Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

The experience i had in 54hrs is unimaginable, i learnt so many things in this short span of time. I learnt how customer influence product, marketing and product growth analysis. It was most experiencing moments i had with life. We developed a product as a team, evaluated its cost and got about 5-6 customers in short span of time.

# Zolo

Zolo SEAL

July 2020 - Present (2 months)

The experience of learning about digital marketing skills along with leadership program was huge gain to my skill set.

GeeksforGeeks
Campus Ambassador
June 2019 - September 2019 (4 months)

Internshala Intern December 2018 - April 2019 (5 months)

learned digital marketing

leadership qualities and public speaking got ehanced.

figured out how to get internship by internshala

communication, event management and interpersonal skills

Money-Wizards
Campus Ambassador
December 2018 - January 2019 (2 months)
Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India

marketing to improve awareness in finance education
learning about finance involved in company
how does a startup raise funds
how does it save from burnout all amazing things like series funding
various investors I learnt a lot from this intern

## Education

Panimalar Engineering College
BE - Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

prince matriculation higher secondary school Higher secondary course, biology (2016 - 2017)